[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
F*ck!
you've already become one.
How would you still have bad luck?
Mungkorn.
Take him back home for a visit.
If there's any misunderstanding, talk it out.
Why you always have cat food with you.
You're just like a cat.
That's why you attract them.
Can you please call me...
Thear the way your mom calls me?
Goodnight,
Thear.
Hey.
You woke up for a run without even telling me.
I saw you were still asleep,
so I didn't want to wake you.
I guess I was having a really good dream.
Cause someone cuddled me last night, I ended up sleeping in.
Why are you in such a rush?
How about another lap?
That's enough for me.
Come on, run with me for just one more lap.
You go run by yourself.
Let's go together. Please?
Look at you.
Are you trying to get a chance to hug me?
Wasn't all that cuddling last night enough for you?
There's no need to pretend to fall.
It was an accident.
You're talking nonsense.
Getting scolded by you in the morning really wakes me up.
I feel like I could run another hundred kilometers.
- Let's go run together. - Then go run by yourself.
I'm heading home.
Hey!
Where are we now?
We've reached Chiang Mai.
In Chiang Mai already?
I only dozed off for a second.
Three hours is just a second to you?
You just left me driving all by myself.
But it's okay. Watching you sleep was actually nice.
Inspector.
See?
I've already told you
to call me Thear.
Thear...
Would you mind if we made a stop first?
The shop is right on the way home.
What kind of shop is that?
A shaved ice place.
Does that mean this whole trip wasn't sweet enough?
The sweetness from Thear
might not be good for my health.
But I think the sweets here
are the best.
Of course.
Wherever you want to eat, I'll take you.
When it comes to spoiling his boyfriend, nobody does it better than Thear.
Oh, it's closed.
I've been wanting to eat here.
Do you really want to have it that badly?
Should we go somewhere else?
It's fine.
I just really like this place.
Sometimes it's not about the taste.
It's more about the vibes.
Alright.
I'll bring you back another day then,
okay?
Let's head back.
Okay.
(Yin as Theartha)
(War as Mungkorn)
(Shane as Phuwin)
(Boss as Lukplub)
(Krit as Kanin)
(Tang as Nadol)
(Tay as Saming)
Hello, Sinthawee.
How are you, Thear?
Are you well-rested yet?
If you are, it's time to get back to work.
What?
Back to...?
Am I really going back to work?
(Yes.)
(The autopsy results are finally out.)
(Ronnaphop's last molar)
had poison hidden inside it.
(He intended to break that tooth to commit suicide.)
And now,
you've been cleared of the charges.
Understood, sir. Thank you so much.
I'm so ready to get back to work now.
(And one more thing.)
Don't forget to thank Mungkorn.
The moment he arrived at the station,
he rushed to get those autopsy results for you.
Yes, sir. I will.
I'll go thank Mungkorn as well.
Thank you, Uncle.
Oh,
the intel reports that
the Black Bull drug has effects similar to a date rape drug.
(Initially, it causes intoxication.)
But after a while,
it triggers an uncontrollable, intense sexual arousal.
If you spot anyone with those symptoms,
you could assume that they've taken the Black Bull drug.
(Copy that, sir.)
(I'll give it my best this time.)
Good.
All set.
You really seem to care about him.
Well, he's my boss.
But thank you anyway, sir.
Whoa!
Hey!
Wow!
Hunglay!
I missed you.
I missed you so much.
I wish I were a bike.
So I could get all those kisses, hugs, and cuddles from you.
I called to get them to speed up the delivery.
Thank you so much.
I finally have a bike to ride to work.
What?
Do you mean we won't go to work together anymore?
I'm finally getting back to work, you know.
Well, congratulations on that.
Oh, acting all happy for me?
Weren't you the one who helped me?
But I'm curious now,
did you help me as a subordinate,
or as a husband?
Well.
Maybe a bit of both.
My mom taught me that
when you're under someone's roof, you should be helpful.
I don't really need you to be helpful.
I much prefer you helping me with something else.
You're completely twisting the idea,
making something meaningful seem ambiguous.
Since it's here, why don't we take it for a ride?
You sure?
Whoa!
You'll get to see just how powerful Hunglay really is.
He needs to warm up a bit. He might not be used to Chiang Mai.
Let's go.
Hold tight.
Let's go!
♪And you look into my eyes,♪
♪It's too much for this heart to keep inside♪
♪Almost forgot how to breathe,♪
♪How could you do this to me?♪
♪Told you to stop, but you wouldn't agree♪
♪With all the evidence I have found,♪
♪Guess I'll have to take you into custody now♪
♪That level of cuteness is against the law♪
♪I must be under your spell, can I blame you at all?♪
I told you so.
Hunglay is the real deal.
Engine's fired up and ready to go.
Ready to go?
We had to pray just to get it started.
He has some tricks
that make him more valuable, you know?
Just like his owner, right?
You weren't even gonna share them?
I'm about to choke on these snacks.
I actually bought some for you, too.
Here.
Want me to feed you?
That won't be necessary.
Careful, you're gonna spill it.
Come on. Cheers.
Let's celebrate you getting back to work.
You got it. Cheers!
What are you trying to do?
You're eating like a messy little kid.
Thank you.
You know, ever since we got back from Phayao,
I'm not sure if you've noticed,
but I feel like I've changed.
You've changed?
Did you eat more or gain weight?
I don't mean that.
My body is still as fit as ever. See?
I'm still healthy.
It's something in my heart.
I just feel much happier now.
I feel like I'm more fulfilled.
Like, I've seen another side of someone.
Maybe someone's opening up to me.
I've been open this whole time.
You just didn't see it.
Then keep it open, okay?
Because from now on,
I won't take my eyes off you.
Why did you bring me here?
Hey.
I've got to take you out for something fun.
So you can relax and unwind.
A bathhouse?
No way.
I can shower by myself.
What kind of guy do you think I am?
Even though I was a playboy and went to those places,
I haven't been there ever since I've been with you.
That won't be necessary.
You should just let someone bathe you like you always do.
Come on, that's not happening.
The only one who gets to bathe me
is you.
This is my regular hangout spot.
They have pool tables, hot springs, saunas, a gym,
and even special massages
From the sound of it,
this place seems like heaven for you.
Do you want to go to heaven with me?
Mungkorn!
Wait, what?
Lukplub.
Phuwin.
What are you guys doing here?
Phuwin was invited to celebrate Thear's return to work.
- I see. - And I missed you so much too.
I wanted to see how you're doing here.
It's good.
There's always something exciting here.
What about you, Thear?
Are you taking good care of my brother like you promised?
Well, I just carried him up here.
All that's left is to have him sit on my lap.
Happy now?
That much?
And...
How did you end up here?
I invited him myself.
If we work together, we should hang out to get to know each other.
Actually, that's not really necessary.
I don't want to be that close to you.
I think staying in my room and reading books would be better.
You just stay cooped up in your room and never meet anyone.
No wonder you're still single.
I'm single, and I'm fine with it.
I enjoy my life.
You've got to give it a try.
You never know until you try.
He's right.
You've got to try.
Oh.
How did you come here with Thear?
Well.
My place is very close to his, so we just came together.
Hold on a second.
Aren't you staying at the police flats?
The police flats were full.
- So I couldn't move in... - Actually, they aren't full.
There are plenty of rooms left.
What?
What's going on here?
The flats in Chiang Mai are quite old.
I suggested that Mungkorn find a place to rent.
That's probably more convenient.
Don't make a big deal out of it.
We're neighbors.
It's normal for us to come together, right?
Right.
Okay.
Come on, let me practice. I'll rack them up again.
Hey, Thear.
Do you have a ring on your ring finger?
Are you married, or did you just put it there?
I...
I'm married.
Why would I put it there for no reason?
When did you get married? Why didn't I know?
It's just someone I'm close to.
Right, Mungkorn?
Hey!
What's the deal?
How come Mungkorn knows but I don't?
Come on, let me see your lover.
Can I see Inspector Thear's sweetheart?
I have to respect them.
If they're not ready,
how can I introduce them?
Are there any more cues?
I want to play billiards too.
Yeah, go get one. It's in locker number six back there.
Yes.
Come on, come on.
Hello, there.
Yes?
Is this your first time here?
I've never seen you around.
Yes, it's my first time.
Are you from here?
No, I'm from Phayao.
I see.
I moved here from Krabi.
I wanted a change of scenery.
The people here are quite lovely.
You've come a long way.
From the south all the way to the north.
The distance might be great,
but our hearts might end up close.
My name is North. What's yours?
Your name is North, but you're from the south?
That's quite a contrast.
I'm Mungkorn.
Wow, Mungkorn.
Such a tough name, but why are you so adorable?
Do you want to play a match with me?
If you can't play well, I can teach you.
Mungkorn.
Is something going on?
The others are waiting.
It's nothing.
Please excuse me.
Not bad.
That's too hard.
That yellow ball.
That's not an easy one.
- It's not that easy. - It's not easy at all.
You have such great skin and body.
That's why people keep hitting on you.
- Who's hitting on me? - That guy.
The one at the pool table.
He was just being friendly.
You can't call that hitting on me.
That's exactly your problem.
You're so naive.
I can tell at a glance
he's got his sights
set on you.
What kind of sights?
You're quite the expert at this.
Like you always have your sights set on others.
Next time,
if someone looks at you like this,
or touches you like this,
I'm stepping right in.
I'm the jealous type.
That won't be necessary.
If anyone tries that and I don't like it,
I'll just push them away.
So, you haven't pushed me away.
Does that mean you like it?
What are you doing?
Hey, Thear!
Get in the water already. What are you waiting for?
Yeah, okay. I'll be right there.
Right.
Hey, Phuwin.
You've known Mungkorn since before you transferred to Mae Sai, right?
Of course.
Thear and I trained him ourselves.
I totally forgot
that Thear was also called in to train the boots.
Mungkorn.
Was Thear scary?
Not really.
He was more like, acting cool and bossy.
He wasn't afraid of me.
Back then, he had someone protecting him.
Wait, what?
Who was it?
Thear's best friend.
Best friend, my a*s.
I don't even want to mention that prick.
How did you pass
the Police Examination when you got tattoos like that?
I got them after that.
I was thinking of getting more.
Wanna get my face tattooed on you?
It'll protect you better than a yantra.
I'll pass on that.
It looks ugly.
Take that.
How do you like that, Kanin?
Someone like you deserves someone like Nadol to shut you up.
What's wrong?
I'm thirsty.
Let me grab a drink.
I'm parched.
Hello.
- Oh! - Hey!
You again?
Do you work here?
Oh, no.
The staff went to the restroom, so I'm just helping them.
Would you like something to drink?
A glass of beer, please.
Beer? Sure thing.
So, what do you do for a living?
I work as a host.
I see.
You're quite the sweet talker and good at pleasing people.
But with your looks, you could definitely do it too.
You might even have guests lining up for you.
Thanks.
But I'll pass. It's not really my thing.
No problem.
But if you ever change your mind...
Here's my card.
Here is your beer.
Thanks.
Please let go of my boyfriend's hand.
He's your boyfriend?
He didn't mention he had one.
Well, he's not my boyfriend.
He's my husband.
Okay.
I see.
I'll back off then.
See? I told you he was trying to hit on you.
If you go around telling people like that,
everyone is going to find out.
Why not just put it in the headlines?
If I could, it'd be a big one.
So I can let everyone know that we are
husbands.
Are you that thirsty?
Are you okay?
Is it too hot in here?
I'm fine.
But it feels like I'm burning up from the inside.
What do you mean by that?
I don't know.
I've never felt like this before.
You might be sick.
Should we head back? I'll take you home.
I'm not going back.
What are you doing?
The others are in the room.
You like excitement, don't you?
You really wanted it earlier.
Stop it.
Mungkorn.
Hey.
What's wrong with you two?
If you're feeling hot, just go outside.
Yeah. It's freaking hot.
I can't take it anymore.
Excuse me.
Hey, Mungkorn.
I think Thear took what I said a little too seriously.
He's taking really good care of Mungkorn.
But I think he's taking it too seriously.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I think it's strange.
They're acting like a couple.
I don't think so.
He already said he's married.
He probably doesn't think of Mungkorn as more than a brother.
Is that so?
Okay.
Hey, Mungkorn.
What's wrong with you? You're acting weird.
I don't know.
I feel so hot inside.
And I'm dizzy now.
Your body's not hot at all.
Hey!
Mungkorn!
What has gotten into you?
You're not usually like this.
This is not you at all.
You don't seem like yourself.
It seems like you're drunk.
I'm not even drunk.
I've only had one glass of beer.
Beer.
Beer?
The Black Bull drug has effects similar to a date rape drug.
Initially, it causes intoxication.
But after a while,
it triggers an uncontrollable, intense sexual arousal.
Hold up.
I think you've been drugged.
Your symptoms are definitely caused by that Black Bull drug.
Drugged?
Am I going to be okay?
You're going to be fine.
I'll take care of you.
Let's head home first.
I'll tell the others you're not feeling well.
Okay?
Okay.
That's better.
Let's go.
Watch your step.
Come on.
Sit here for a moment.
Let me call Nadol first.
I'll get you some water.
Stay right here.
Alright.
Okay.
Hello, Nadol. I need some advice.
Someone I know might have been drugged with the Black Bull drug.
Is there any way to help with it?
(You have to help them stay conscious.)
(Give them some cold water to drink.)
(Maybe have them take a shower, soak in the tub, and get some rest.)
(But you have to be careful)
(because once the drug takes effect,)
(it can be quite intense.)
Why can it be intense?
(It'll cause them to release all their pent-up emotions.)
What kind of emotions?
(Sexual desires.)
Mungkorn.
Where did you go? I told you to wait here.
Sh*t.
What have you been doing?
I just went to the toilet.
Oh, okay.
I've talked with Nadol.
He said drinking plenty of water is the way to go.
Here you go.
Sure.
I'll drink lots of water.
Just as you said, Inspector.
Hey, wait.
Why are you spilling it everywhere?
I'm just a little too thirsty.
My shirt is all soaked.
Let me take it off then.
Hey.
I think we'd better head to the bedroom.
Let's go.
I'm not really sleepy.
I'd rather do something fun instead.
What are you doing?
What do husbands usually do?
We were only faking it last time.
Maybe we should make it real.
Wait, wait.
Mung...
Mungkorn.
Hey.
I think...
the drug is really kicking in now.
It has nothing to do with the drug.
I'm simply following my heart.
Seductive like this...
Don't you like it?
I like it.
I like it, but...
Mung...
If you want me to get even wilder,
I'll give you exactly what you want.
We should stop.
I don't think this is right.
This is clearly the drug talking.
Are you ready to see fiery Mungkorn?
I really like this.
This version of you.
Can I get something even wilder?
Mungkorn.
The drug's taken over you.
I'm not high.
I...
I can't hold back anymore.
We have to do it right now.
We can't do that, not right now.
You're under the influence.
If not now, then when?
Don't be too stubborn.
No, wait. It's not right.
No! Whoa, Mungkorn!
Hold on, we can't. Trust me.
Hey!
Mungkorn.
Listen to me.
Just listen to me.
How about this?
Why don't we do it in the room instead?
If someone walks by,
it won't look good.
I'm not ashamed at all.
I want to do it right now.
Mungkorn.
But I'm too stingy.
I can't have anyone seeing you naked.
I wouldn't be able to stand it.
I want you all to myself.
I'm going to make tonight
truly special.
Sit here first.
Why don't we do it on the bed?
What are we doing here?
We need to make it more exciting.
Let's do it in the tub instead, okay?
But it's cold.
It's okay. I'll warm you right up.
Wait, hold on.
Mungkorn.
Don't you want to kiss me?
Am I not cute enough?
Of course you are.
You're the cutest person I know.
If I'm cute, then kiss me.
Hold up.
Look.
We shouldn't be doing this
while you're unconscious.
Then what do I have to do
to please you?
Could you tell me?
Listen to me.
You don't have to do anything.
I like you just the way you are.
I'll run the water for you.
Come on, stand up.
Let's go in the tub, okay?
Inspector,
I feel like I have no strength left.
It's okay.
You can just fall asleep if you want.
I'll look after you.
You're up, honey?
You were pretty naughty last night.
So you're my first?
I was more than happy to be.
What the f*ck are you doing?
Tonight's gonna be a good time.
Hey!
What are you doing?
♪Trying so hard not to cross the line,♪
♪But the more I run, the more you're on my mind♪
♪If you're gonna love me, don't break the deal we made♪
♪Don't break my heart, remember what you said?♪
♪Let's call off the deal and let our hearts decide♪
♪From contracting parties to lovers, does that sound alright?♪
♪It's time you became mine♪